<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie XXI</string>

    <string name="tab_text_1">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tv Show</string>
    <string name="judul_film">Movie title :</string>
    <string name="tanggal_rilis">Release Date :</string>
    <string name="rating_film">Movie Rating :</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="original_language">Original Language</string>
    <string name="durasi">Duration</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="detail">Detail Movie</string>

    <string-array name="data_judul">
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Maze Runner: The Death Cure</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>Spiderman</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rating">
        <item>68%</item>
        <item>83%</item>
        <item>65%</item>
        <item>68%</item>
        <item>80%</item>
        <item>75%</item>
        <item>64%</item>
        <item>70%</item>
        <item>58%</item>
        <item>84%</item>
        <item>66%</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rilis">
        <item>December 7, 2018</item>
        <item>April 25, 2018</item>
        <item>December 15, 2018</item>
        <item>November 21, 2018</item>
        <item>October 24, 2018</item>
        <item>October 3, 2018</item>
        <item>October 19, 2018</item>
        <item>January 10, 2018</item>
        <item>November 21, 2018</item>
        <item>December 6, 2018</item>
        <item>September 28, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_status">
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_bahasa">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_durasi">
        <item>2h 24m</item>
        <item>2h 29m</item>
        <item>1h 54m</item>
        <item>2h 10m</item>
        <item>2h 15m</item>
        <item>2h 16m</item>
        <item>2h 2m</item>
        <item>2h 24m</item>
        <item>1h 56m</item>
        <item>1h 57m</item>
        <item>1h 52m</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_deskripsi">
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater
            kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans
            to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way
            is Arthur Curry, Orms half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too
            large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows:
            Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones,
            artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of
            reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate
            of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian
            beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world,
            discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns
            this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent
            with ties to his familys past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.</item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist
            John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock n roll band Queen
            in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercurys increasingly wild lifestyle
            starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding
            a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</item>
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist
            Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack
            coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Allys career takes off, the personal side
            of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own
            internal demons.</item>
        <item>Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup détat is taking place in
            Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.</item>
        <item>Thomas leads his group of escaped Gladers on their final and most dangerous mission yet.
            To save their friends, they must break into the legendary Last City, a WCKD-controlled
            labyrinth that may turn out to be the deadliest maze of all. Anyone who makes it out alive
            will get answers to the questions the Gladers have been asking since they first arrived in the maze.</item>
        <item>A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the
            corrupt English crown.</item>
        <item>Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a
            spider-man. When Wilson "Kingpin" Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the
            Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.</item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but
            accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon,
            he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization
            looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mazerunner</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_judul2">
        <item>Freaks</item>
        <item>Solo: A Star Wars Story</item>
        <item>T-34</item>
        <item>Jurassic Galaxy</item>
        <item>Master Z: Ip Man Legacy</item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>Black Panther</item>
        <item>Hotel Transylvania 3: Summer Vacation</item>
        <item>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</item>
        <item>The Meg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rating2">
        <item>69%</item>
        <item>66%</item>
        <item>55%</item>
        <item>37%</item>
        <item>54%</item>
        <item>75%</item>
        <item>74%</item>
        <item>68%</item>
        <item>73%</item>
        <item>59%</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rilis2">
        <item>September 8, 2018</item>
        <item>May 15, 2018</item>
        <item>December 27, 2018</item>
        <item>August 20, 2018</item>
        <item>December 20, 2018</item>
        <item>May 10, 2018</item>
        <item>February 13, 2018</item>
        <item>June 28, 2018</item>
        <item>July 13, 2018</item>
        <item>August 9, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_status2">
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
        <item>Released</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_bahasa2">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Russian</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Cantonese</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_durasi2">
        <item>1h 45m</item>
        <item>2h 15m</item>
        <item>2h 19m</item>
        <item>1h 16m</item>
        <item>1h 47m</item>
        <item>2h 1m</item>
        <item>2h 14m</item>
        <item>1h 37m</item>
        <item>2h 28m</item>
        <item>1h 53m</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_deskripsi2">
        <item>Kept locked inside the house by her father, 7-year-old Chloe lives in fear and fascination
            of the outside world, where Abnormals create a constant threat - or so she believes. When
            a mysterious stranger offers her a glimpse of whats really happening outside, Chloe soon
            finds that while the truth isnt so simple, the danger is very real.</item>
        <item>Through a series of daring escapades deep within a dark and dangerous criminal underworld,
            Han Solo meets his mighty future copilot Chewbacca and encounters the notorious gambler Lando
            Calrissian.</item>
        <item>In 1944, a courageous group of Russian soldiers managed to escape from German captivity
            in a half-destroyed legendary T-34 tank. Those were the times of unforgettable bravery,
            fierce fighting, unbreakable love, and legendary miracles.</item>
        <item>In the near future, a ship of space explorers crash land on an unknown planet. Theyre
            soon met with some of their worst fears as they discover the planet is inhabited by monstrous
            dinosaurs.</item>
        <item>Following his defeat by Master Ip, Cheung Tin Chi (Zhang) tries to make a life with his
            young son in Hong Kong, waiting tables at a bar that caters to expats. But it s not long
            before the mix of foreigners, money, and triad leaders draw him once again to the fight.</item>
        <item>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys
            to save a boys life.</item>
        <item>King TChalla returns home from America to the reclusive, technologically advanced
            African nation of Wakanda to serve as his countrys new leader. However, TChalla soon
            finds that he is challenged for the throne by factions within his own country as well as
            without. Using powers reserved to Wakandan kings, TChalla assumes the Black Panther mantel
            to join with girlfriend Nakia, the queen-mother, his princess-kid sister, members of the
            Dora Milaje (the Wakandan special forces) and an American secret agent, to prevent Wakanda
            from being dragged into a world war.</item>
        <item>Dracula, Mavis, Johnny and the rest of the Drac Pack take a vacation on a luxury Monster
            Cruise Ship, where Dracula falls in love with the ship’s captain, Ericka, who’s secretly a
            descendant of Abraham Van Helsing, the notorious monster slayer.</item>
        <item>When an IMF mission ends badly, the world is faced with dire consequences. As Ethan
            Hunt takes it upon himself to fulfill his original briefing, the CIA begin to question
            his loyalty and his motives. The IMF team find themselves in a race against time, hunted
            by assassins while trying to prevent a global catastrophe.</item>
        <item>A deep sea submersible pilot revisits his past fears in the Mariana Trench, and
            accidentally unleashes the seventy foot ancestor of the Great White Shark believed to be
            extinct.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_poster2">
        <item>@drawable/poster_freak</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_solo</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_t34</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_jurassic</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_masterz</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool2</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_blackpanther</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hotel</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mission</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_themeg</item>
    </array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
